

Hello, I'm Iliana

https://www.behance.net/iliana-ng
https://www.linkedin.com/in/iliana-n/
iliana.n.gonzalez@gmail.com

Why hire me?

I help organizations get to know their users, improving the usability, accessibility, and pleasure provided in the interaction with the product, trying to develop new ways to make them happy. This might mean creating a new product or service, or it might just mean improving what's already there saving time and money.

I'm an autodidactic and proactive person, always hungry for new challenges and innovations.



Research to understand project requirements and define uses cases



Gather Ideas to synthesize the research and brainstorm possible solutions.



Design to refine user interface and create prototypes



Test and Iterate to identify improvements



I always take focus on customers concern in order to get the best final solution according to their goals



The methods and techniques I use within each phase of my process may vary depending on the design challenges.

Experience

Apr 2019 - Present

UX & UI designer

Oktana Corporation

Oktana is a team of innovators, builders, designers and strategists dedicated to delivering exceptionally crafted client solutions in the Salesforce space.

https://www.oktana.com

In this opportunity, I'm working as a UX/UI designer.

We help organizations to improve the usability, accessibility, the pleasure provided in the interaction with the product and the brand of the clients

March 2018 - Apr 2019

UX & UI designer

Tata Consultancy Services

Tata Consultancy Services operate on a global scale, with a diverse talent base of over 411,102 associates representing 147 nationalities, across 46 countries

https://www.tcs.com/

In this opportunity, I have been growing as a leader and as a UX/VD designer working every day with large clients and projects.

I have the responsibility to lead a team and validate that every development aspect respects our UX/VD rules and guidelines. Also, I have the owner of the releases, so I need to focus on the details to get the best solutions to our customers.

December 2017 - March 2018

Web graphic designer

WestOcean

WestOcean is a business that is in charge of the largest lottery agency as WinTrillions and Lottokings

https://www.wintrillions.com/about-wintrillions https://www.lottokings.com/about

I had the great opportunity to work as a designer for many projects within the firm.

My primary responsibility was to build and/or alter designs to keep the users engaged int the platform.

September 2015 - December 2017

Uisual designer and web developer

Vix Inc.

Vix creates content that sparks curiosity. With 70 million social followers and over 1.4 billion views every month, VIX is one of the largest video publishers in the world.

https://www.vix.com/en/corp

It was the first large company that I have the opportunity to work on it. This was one of the best experience of my career to grow, meet and work with many people. I learned a lot about tech, design, agile methodologies and also personnel management.

I worked as a web designer and front-end development for responsive web sites.

February 2015 - March 2016

UX designer

Freelance Talleres Possa

Talleres Possa is a small company dedicated to the mechanical maintenance of forklifts.

It was my first serious client and the first attempt to open a company, this company was looking for a personal solution for internal communication with customers and the ability to synchronize the data with the owner's agenda, in order to make it easy to contact customers.

In conjunction with a developer, we carry out the complete development of the web application.

Education

March 2014- December 2016

Escuela de Comunicación Social

Technical graphic designer

March 2010- December 2011

Anglo

Senior four degree from ANGLO English Institute

Skills

